Hey, everyone.
My name is Sahil and I'm one of the engineers here at Tessl.
I'm going to be in New York and in Boston on the 16th and 17th of September,
talking about how we've built our software factory here at Tessl
and what engineering looks like in an AI native world.
I'm going to be diving into the components that we've built out,
why they're there, why they're useful, the mistakes that we've made along the way,
the sort of metrics that we focused on early that actually didn't end up helping
us, and the ones that actually did, and all the different quirks and features
that ended up building out the factory that we have today.
This is going to be a much more practical look into the factory that we have here
at Tessl and some of the specifics on how it works
and why we made some of the decisions that we did.
Go to tessl.io/events and I hope to see you all there.